{
    "id": "609f743ab85a4c0db8b97e1989c0df36",
    "title": "Party Phrasal Verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8324baa88cd941d7b2eb231d3c40bad0",
            "title": "Party Phrasal Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Please blow .................................... these balloons and hang them around the room.",
                    "description": "To blow up balloons is to fill them with air. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you turn ................................. the volume a bit?",
                    "description": "To turn up the volume is to raise the volume.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tomorrow I am going to blow ................................. 39 candles on my birthday cake.",
                    "description": "To blow out candles is to extinguish them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "over",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We pulled .............................. a surprise party for the newly married couple.",
                    "description": "To pull off something is to succeed in doing something difficult.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They were all dressed ................................... for the party.",
                    "description": "To dress up is to wear better/fancier clothes than you usually wear.",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "up",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoy hanging ................................. with my friends at my house.",
                    "description": "To hang out with your friends is to spend time relaxing.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "out",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When will you come to pick me ...............................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am eating ................................... a lot these days.",
                    "description": "To eat out is to eat in a restaurant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I invited her to tea but she turned ………………………….. my offer.",
                    "description": "To turn down an offer is to reject it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to keep asking her …………………….. until she says ‘Yes’.",
                    "description": "To ask someone out is to invite them to come with you to a place.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cheer ……………………… You will win next time.",
                    "description": "This is an expression used to encourage someone to have a more positive attitude.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children cracked ………………………… as soon as the clown arrived on the scene.",
                    "description": "To crack up is to burst out laughing. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "on",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}